Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Areas / Activities, Series IV
  - Women 's concerns
    - Correspondence and Staff Records
      - Esther Byu, 1988 June-1996 August
        - Letters out, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 10)
        - Letters out, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
        - Letters out, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
        - Letters out, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - Letters out, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - Letters out, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - Letters out, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
        - Letters out, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Mizuho Matsuda, 1984-1987
        - Correspondence and documents, 1984-1987 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 13, Folder 18)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988-1993 (Box 13, Folder 19)
        - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989-1996 (Box 13, Folder 20)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 100, Folder 26)
        - Correspondence re. Women 's Concerns publications., 1988-1996 (Box 13, Folder 21)
        - Correspondence re. Women 's Concerns publications., 1988-1996 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Financial Records
      - Budget, programmes, 1985-1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Budget, programmes, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Budget, programmes, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Programme expenses, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Income expenditure report, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, Reports
      - Minutes of the 1st meeting of the Women 's programme committee of CCA, 7-9 Sept.1981, Singapore (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Programme committee meeting of Women' s Concerns, minutes of the CCA staff meeting,1-4 Mar.1983, Singapore (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Minutes of the programme committee on Women 's Concerns, 17-23 Feb.1986, Hua Hin,Thailand. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Women 's Concerns programme committee, Five year programme projection 1986-1990, CCA women network (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Vision statement,programme projection, 1986-1995 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - General committee minutes 1987, working group reports (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Minutes and reports, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Programme reports, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Programme and travel schedules, 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Women 's Concerns monthly reports, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Notes, reports, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Travel plan, programme reports, 1989-1996 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 1992 programme evaluation, 1993 programme (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Travel reports, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Travel reports, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Women Power Sharing Survey: A-H. Resource data collection., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20A)
      - Women Power Sharing Survey: H-I. Resource data collection., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20B)
      - Women Power Sharing Survey: I-M. Resource data collection., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20C)
    - Conferences, Consultations, Workshops
      - Asian Women 's Conference to Assess the Impact of the UN Decade for Women., 1985 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - CCA-WCC Joint Consultation on "Militarization and its effects on Women in Asia",1-7 Dec.1986, Bangkok,Thailand (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - CCA-WCC Joint Consultation on "Militarization and its effects on Women in Asia",1-7 Dec.1986, Bangkok,Thailand. (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - NCC Ecumenical Women Leaders in Asia, 11-15 Jan.1986,Bangkok, Thailand. (Box 14, Folder 23A)
      - East Asia Sub-regional Women 's Conference, 7-10 May.1987, Fukuoka, Japan. (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - South Asia Sub-Regional Women 's Conference,27 Feb.-3 Mar.1987, Kandy, Sri Lanka. (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Consultation on "Creation and Suffering Peoples of Asia",14-19 August,1989, Bangkok, Thailand. (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Northeast Asia Women 's Consultation, 25-29 Oct.1989, Kwangju,Korea. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Northeast Asia Women 's Consultation, 25-29 Oct.1989, Kwangju,Korea. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - South Asia Sub-Regional Consultation for Women, 17-22 Jul.1989, Madras, India. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Rural Women Leaders' Consultation,7-17 June.1989, Tagaytay city, Philippines. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Rural Women Leaders' Consultation,7-17 June.1989, Tagaytay city, Philippines. (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - South Asia Sub-Regional Consultation, 17-22 Jul.1989, Gurukul Theological Campus, Madras, India. (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - CCA Pre-Assembly Women 's Forum, 31 May.-3 June.1990, Laguna, Philippines. (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - CCA Pre-Assembly Women 's Forum, 31 May.-3 June.1990, Laguna, Philippines. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - NCC Women 's Secretaries' Consultation, 21-26 Apr.1990, Lahore, Pakistan. (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Consultation on " Militarisation", 19-25 June.1992, Okinawa, Japan. (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Consultation on " Militarisation", 19-25 June.1992, Okinawa, Japan. (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - 1st Asian Women Christian Artists Consultation,9-13 Sept.1992, Hong Kong. List of participants. (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - 1st Asian Women Christian Artists Consultation,9-13 Sept.1992, Hong Kong. Artists stories. (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Gender Partnership workshop report, 4-10 Oct.1993, Hong Kong. (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - NCC Women 's Desk secretaries' Working Consultation, 10-15 Feb.1993,Port Dickson, Malaysia. (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - NCC Women 's Desk secretaries' Working Consultation, 10-15 Feb.1993,Port Dickson, Malaysia. (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Consultation on 'Partnership of Women and Men in God",20-25 Feb.1994, Philippines. (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - National Women Leaders Planning Workshop, 25-30 Aug.1994, YMCA, Bangkok, Thailand. (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Workshop on " Gender and Development", 19-25 Oct.1994, Chiang Mai, Thailand. Proceeding. (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Workshop on " Gender and Development", 19-25 Oct.1994, Chiang Mai, Thailand. Income and expenditure report. (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - CCA Pre- Assemble Women 's Forum, 4-7 June 1995, Colombo, Sri Lanka (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - CCA Pre- Assemble Women 's Forum, 4-7 June 1995, Colombo, Sri Lanka (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Workshop on Women and Beijing Churches' Response, 1-3 Aug.1995, Hong Kong. Programme, proceeding. (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Women 's Concerns programme and activities of 1996. (Box 15, Folder 24)
      - Indo-China Women 's Consultation on " Sub- Regional Conference on AIDS and Migrant Concerns, 12-17 June.1996, Bangkok, Thailand. (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Sub -Regional Conference on AIDS and Migrant Concerns, 12-17 Jul.1996,Taiwan. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Workshop on Violence against Women,16-20 Apr.1996. Hong Kong. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Gender Awareness and Sensitivity Course,7-13 Sept.1997, Philippines. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Gender Awareness and Sensitivity Course,3-9 Nov.1997, Bangladesh. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Gender Awareness and Sensitivity Course, 27Jun.- 4 Jul.1998, Sri Lanka. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Gender Awareness and Sensitivity Course,7-13 June.1998, Thailand. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - CCA Pre-Assembly Women 's Forum, 27-30 May.2000, Tomohon, Indonesia. (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - CCA Pre-Assembly Women 's Forum, 27-30 May.2000, Tomohon, Indonesia (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Joint partners committee writers' workshop,19-26 Jan.2000,Mendez, Cavite, Philippines. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Related Organizations
      - World Council Of Churches. Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Asian Women Institute, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Committee for Asian Women. Reports, planned programme., 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Lutheran World Federation. Correspondence, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Publications.
      - Asian Women: Our Lives, Our Faith, Our God., 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Collected Materials
      - The Cost of tea, A question of Morality, A community of life By Alison O' Grady., 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Anti - Prostitution Activities in Japan published by Association of Anti - Prostitution Activity, Japan., 1984 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Articles on feminist theology, 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous articles, 1982-1996 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Research paper: The Transnational Sex- Exploitation of Thai Women by Siriporn Skrobanek, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - APDC Newsletter Vol.2, No.2, 1983 February (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Contours, Vol.1, No.2, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Women and Peace, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Papers from CCA 8th Assembly Women 's Forum., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Lawasia Child Exploitation seminar, 1985. Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia. (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Theology Consultation, 8-13 Apr.1985, Chiang Mai, Thailand (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Timbangan Consumer 's Journal, Vol.4, No.1., 1985 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Asian Churchwomen Speak, Statement from the CCA Women 's Forum, 22--25 June.1985, Seoul, Korea (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Association for Theological Education in Southeast Asia. Accreditation team report., 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Labor Day Statement: Women Workers and the Unfinished Struggle for an Eight- Hours Works Day, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Patpong Community Newsletter: A Women 's Training Participation Project, 1986July-1987June (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Project proposal: Skill Training Workshop for Women Instructors, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Visit to Mannar-NCC Women 's Commission., 1987 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Decade Link, No.3, December 1988 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Pacific Conference of Churches Women s Desk Report on " Participation of Women in Church and society"., 1989 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - CCA consultation " A Search for a Relevant Ecclesiology in Asia" 30 Jan-3 Feb.1989, Chiang Mai, Thailand. (Box 16, Folder 36)
      - Asian Women perspectives Christian Theology by Dulcie P. Abraham., undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
      - Short story of the Chateau de Bossey., undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
      - Maori Concerns, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
      - Preliminary proposal for the establishment of a Family Life Institute at Central Philippines University, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
      - Theology from the point of view of Asian Women by Sr. Mary John Mananzan., undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
      - Including "Women in Black" gathering, "Trinjan Quilt Project", "Women in Theological Education in Africa, Asia, the Pacific, Latin America and the Caribbean", 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Youth Program
    This series is primarily composed of administrative records, conference and consultation materials, correspondence, and materials relating to both the Rural Youth Program (RYP) and World Youth Program (WYP). Administrative records contain general correspondence as well as correspondence from the Youth Secretary in addition to materials from partner agencies with project reports and correspondence. Conference and consultation records contain correspondence, program and lecture papers, project proposals, publicity materials, and travel schedules and expenses related to Youth Assembly and Youth Forums. The CCA Youth Committee files contain reports and meeting minutes, and country files comprise correspondence, papers, and project reports. This series also contains papers and correspondence from Youth conferences on the topics of leadership and social concerns and contain conference papers, minutes, and reports, planning materials, and travel arrangements as well as numerous Youth conference delegate and steward applications.
    - Administrative records
      - General
        - Accounting System, 1997-1998 (Box 161, Folder 1)
        - Asian Ecumenical Course, 1988 (Box 161, Folder 2)
        - Asian Ecumenical Education Exchange, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 3)
        - Asian Human Rights Commission, 1993-1998 (Box 161, Folder 4)
        - Asian Working Group, 1994 (Box 161, Folder 5)
        - Bible Studies, Reclaiming the Cross, 2000-2001 (Box 161, Folder 6)
        - Bible Workshop: Reading the Bible Through Asian Eyes, correspondence, 1996 (Box 161, Folder 7)
        - Bible Workshop: Reading the Bible Through Asian Eyes, papers and reports, 1996 (Box 161, Folder 8)
        - Bible Workshop: Reading the Bible Through Asian Eyes, presentations and worship, 1996 (Box 161, Folder 9)
        - Budgets, programmatic and travel reports, 1991-1992, no date (Box 161, Folder 10)
        - Budgets, programmatic and travel reports, 1993-1998 (Box 161, Folder 11)
        - Budgets and Finance, 1992-1997 (Box 161, Folder 12)
        - Building a Culture of Peace Workshop, 2000 (Box 161, Folder 13)
        - Cambodia Human Rights, 1990-1994 (Box 161, Folder 14)
        - Cambodian Christian Youth Association, 1998-2000 (Box 161, Folder 15)
        - CCA/UNESCAP, correspondence, 1992, 1996-1997 (Box 161, Folder 16)
        - CCA/UNESCAP, reports, 1988-1993, no date (Box 161, Folder 17)
        - CCA/UNESCAP, reports, 1994-1996 (Box 161, Folder 18)
        - "Christian Concern for Development" annotated bibliography, 1970 March (Box 161, Folder 19)
        - Christones Tour, 1971 (Box 161, Folder 20)
        - Communications: programmatic and travel reports, 1992-1997 (Box 161, Folder 21)
        - Development and service: budgets, programmatic and travel reports, 1993-1996 (Box 161, Folder 22)
        - Ecumenical Christian Centre, India, Youth Department, 1982 (Box 161, Folder 23)
        - Ecumenical Refugee and Migration News, 1994-1996 (Box 161, Folder 24)
        - Ecumenical Scholarships Program, 1995-1998 (Box 162, Folder 1)
        - Ecumenical Youth Council in Europe: Reconciliation as a Means for Sustainable Peace, 2004 (Box 162, Folder 2)
        - Education Desk: courses, programmatic and travel reports, 1992-1997 (Box 162, Folder 3)
        - Human Rights Training Workshop in Delhi, India: budget and evaluations, 1996 (Box 162, Folder 4)
        - Human Rights Training Workshop in Delhi, India: correspondence, travel, and applications, 1996 (Box 162, Folder 5)
        - International Affairs, CCA-IA Reports re: militarism in Asia, 1986-1990 (Box 162, Folder 6)
        - International Affairs, PP21 Conference planning, 1989-1993 (Box 162, Folder 7)
        - International Affairs, programmatic and travel reports, 1991-1992, no date (Box 162, Folder 8)
        - International Affairs, programmatic and travel reports, 1993-1994 (Box 162, Folder 9)
        - International Affairs, programmatic and travel reports, 1995-1996 (Box 162, Folder 10)
        - International Youth Exchange Committee meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 162, Folder 11)
        - International Youth Exchange correspondence, 1965-1971 (Box 162, Folder 12)
        - International Youth Exchange papers, 1965-1971 (Box 162, Folder 13)
        - International Youth Exchange World Research Project in Asia, 1968 (Box 162, Folder 14)
        - Kobe Youth Center, newsletters and reports, 1999-2000 (Box 162, Folder 15)
        - Library and Archives, acquisitions and procedures, 1994-1995 (Box 162, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous papers, 1966-1975 (Box 162, Folder 17)
        - Miscellaneous papers, 1976-1977 (Box 162, Folder 18)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. World Youth Project incl. committee minutes, program activities, 1992-1996 (Box 163, Folder 1)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. Ecumenical Youth Action workcamps, Youth Conference on New Paradigms for the Future, 1994-1995 (Box 163, Folder 2)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. Ecumenical Youth Action workcamps, Youth delegates for 10th assembly, 1994-1995 (Box 163, Folder 3)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. CCA-UN-ESCAP Training workshop for Trainers in Urban/Rural Youth Work, 1993-1996 (Box 163, Folder 4)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. CCA-UN-ESCAP Training workshop for Trainers in Urban/Rural Youth Work, Youth Consultation Seoul, 1994-1996 (Box 163, Folder 5)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WYP budget and finances, 1992-1996 (Box 163, Folder 6)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WYP budget and reports, Indochina visit, Keadilan newsletter, 1991-1996 (Box 163, Folder 7)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. Keadilan newsletter, Indochina, World Youth Projects 1996 committee meeting, 1993-1996 (Box 163, Folder 8)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WYP finances, Indochina visit and reports, AIDS Sunday, 1992-1993 (Box 163, Folder 9)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. CCA AIDS Workshop on Liturgy Oct. 1993, 1992-1994 (Box 163, Folder 10)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. General Secretary's report, Executive Staff correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 163, Folder 11)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WSCF Joint Committee meeting, WCC Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 163, Folder 12)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WCC Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 163, Folder 13)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WCC Correspondence, Ecumenical Youth Work camp, 1991-1996 (Box 179, Folder 15)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. WCC meetings and correspondence, Ecumenical Youth Work camp, Global Ministries United Methodist Church, UN-ESCAP funding, 1992-1997 (Box 179, Folder 16)
        - Misc. papers and correspondence incl. CCA-UN-ESCAP Training workshop for Trainers in Urban/Rural Youth Work, YWSCF correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 179, Folder 17)
        - Mission and Evangelism, correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 162, Folder 19)
        - Mission and Evangelism, programmatic and travel reports, 1992-1996 (Box 162, Folder 20)
        - Personnel, procedures and applications, 1988, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box 162, Folder 21)
        - Preliminary Program Plan for Development and Service, 1998-1999 (Box 162, Folder 22)
        - Programme Thrust, pamphlets, 1991-1995 (Box 162, Folder 23)
        - Regional Youth Networking, correspondence re: ASEM 2000 People's Forum and UN Conference Against Racism, 2000-2001 (Box 162, Folder 24)
        - Regional Youth Secretaries, standards, procedures, and reports of related organizations, 1981-1982 (Box 162, Folder 25)
        - Relations outside of Asia, 1986-1993 (Box 162, Folder 26)
        - Reports, NCC in Pakistan, 1993-1995 (Box 162, Folder 27)
        - Reports, Youth Desk, 1995-2000 (Box 162, Folder 28)
        - RYP/WYP project reports, 1999-2000 (Box 164, Folder 1)
        - RYP/WYP project reports, 2000-2001 (Box 164, Folder 2)
        - RYP/WYP project reports by region, 2000-2001 (Box 164, Folder 3)
        - Saving Sharing Project, 1996-1998 (Box 164, Folder 4)
        - Social and Economic Development, 1996-2007 (Box 164, Folder 5)
        - South Asia Ecumenical Partnership, 2002-2004 (Box 164, Folder 6)
        - Training for development work in Asia, 1996-1998 (Box 164, Folder 7)
        - Travel arrangements, Youth Desk, 1997-2002 (Box 164, Folder 8)
        - Travel reports, Associate General Secretary re: program coordination, 1992-1995 (Box 164, Folder 9)
        - Travel schedules and plans, CCA executive staff, 1992-2000 (Box 164, Folder 10)
        - UN Economic and Social Commission for Asia Pacific, 1996-1997 (Box 164, Folder 11)
        - Workshop for Small Project Fund Holders in Asia held in Korea, 1998 (Box 164, Folder 12)
        - Workshops on Ecology and human rights, 1996 (Box 164, Folder 13)
        - Workshop, worship, 1997 (Box 164, Folder 14)
        - Young Women Training Workshop in Yangon, Myanmar, correspondence, 1997 (Box 164, Folder 15)
        - Young Women Training Workshop in Yangon, Myanmar, planning materials and program reports, 1991-1998 (Box 164, Folder 16)
        - Young Women Training Workshop in Yangon, Myanmar, report, 1997 (Box 164, Folder 17)
        - Youth Finance, 1970 (Box 164, Folder 18)
        - Youth Fund, applications: Australia-India, 2001 (Box 164, Folder 19)
        - Youth Fund, applications: India-Korea, 2001 (Box 164, Folder 20)
        - Youth Fund, applications: Malaysia-Vietnam, 2001 (Box 164, Folder 21)
        - Youth Internship, 2000 (Box 164, Folder 22)
        - Youth Leadership Programme Reports, 1972 (Box 164, Folder 23)
        - Youth newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box 164, Folder 24)
        - Youth Projects in Pakistan, New Zealand, Malaysia, Korea, Indonesia, India, 1977-1981 (Box 165, Folder 1)
      - Conferences and consultations
        - Asian Area Youth Workcamp, Lampung, 1976 (Box 165, Folder 2)
        - Asian Christian Youth Assembly, Bible study outline, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 3)
        - Asian Christian Youth Assembly, program and lecture papers, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 4)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: background papers, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 5)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: follow-up documents, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 6)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: planning papers, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 7)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: report, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 8)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: situation papers, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 9)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: UN papers, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 10)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: workshops, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 11)
        - Asian Christian Youth Consultation for Development, Hong Kong: worship services papers, 1970 July (Box 165, Folder 12)
        - Asia Mission Conference, 25 Apr.-5 May 1994, Seoul, Korea (Box 165, Folder 13)
        - Asia Mission Conference steward applications, 25 Apr-5 May 1994, Seoul, Korea (Box 165, Folder 14)
        - Asian Students and Youth Group (ASYG) in Bangalore, India, 1992-1993 March (Box 165, Folder 15)
        - Asian Students and Youth Group (ASYG) 2000: correspondence, letters in, 1997-1999 (Box 165, Folder 16)
        - Asian Students and Youth Group (ASYG) 2000: correspondence, letters out, 1996-1999 (Box 165, Folder 17)
        - Asian Students and Youth Group (ASYG) 2000: project proposal, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 18)
        - Asia Youth Assembly, general, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 19)
        - Asia Youth Assembly: publicity, 1983-1984 (Box 165, Folder 20)
        - Asia Youth Assembly: travel, schedules and expenses, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 21)
        - Asia Youth Mission, Area reports on sufferings and hope, Hong Kong May 14-23, 1977 (Box 165, Folder 22)
        - Asia Youth Mission, Hong Kong May 14-23 1977, correspondence (Box 165, Folder 23)
        - Asia Youth Mission, Hong Kong May 14-23 1977, Liturgical renewal and pre-assembly papers (Box 165, Folder 24)
        - Asia Youth Resource Conference: applications and correspondence, Hong Kong-New Zealand, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 1)
        - Asia Youth Resource Conference: applications and correspondence, Pakistan-Thailand, 1980 (Box 166, Folder 2)
        - Asia Youth Resource Conference IV: applications and correspondence, Australia-Korea, 1983 (Box 166, Folder 3)
        - Asia Youth Resource Conference IV: applications and correspondence, Malaysia-Thailand, 1983 (Box 166, Folder 4)
        - Asia Youth Resource Conference IV: correspondence re: planning and finances, 1983 (Box 166, Folder 5)
        - Asia Youth Week, budget and expenses, 1987 (Box 166, Folder 6)
        - Asia Youth Week, correspondence and preparatory notes on planning and lectures, 1995-2000 (Box 166, Folder 7)
        - CCA Assembly Youth Forum, planning materials and correspondence, 1999 (Box 166, Folder 8)